dadsworksheets.com 2019-01-17

# Privacy Policy | DadsWorksheets.com

#### Effective: August 9, 2018

We care about your privacy and want you to be informed about how this website handles information. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, and share the information we receive about our visitors and explains the options that are available to you. We’ll try to make this all as clear and as simple as possible, but if you have questions, you can contact us, and we’ll be happy to help. (See the “Contact” link at the bottom of this page.)

### What We Do

Our website allows visitors to print math practice worksheets, use calculators for the purpose of teaching math skills and track progress of students working on math fact memorization. Most functions are free to use without any account or signup, but if you use the site to track progress, you will need to signup for an account to facilitate keeping track of your data between visits. If after you sign up for an account, you can at any time delete your account under the ‘Profile’ page within the ‘Connect’ web application to remove all information we have collected about your use of the website.

This service is provided without charge to visitors, but the site’s operation is paid for by displaying advertising of interest to the visitors. Advertisers and the services that deliver digital advertising to websites such as ours may collect demographic data and monitor your usage of web sites in order to determine what advertising opportunities may be of interest to you.

### Scope of This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy covers all of the information that we collect or receive across the Internet and mobile space through our products, as well as information we collect or receive from visitors to [dadsworksheets.com](https://www.dadsworksheets.com/) (the “Site”) and from registered users of our products. We may change this Policy from time to time (see Changes to the Privacy Policy section below).

### Some Helpful Terminology

We use some phrases in this Privacy Policy that are unique to our business or the online advertising industry. Here are some of the key terms that you’ll need to know to make it easier to review this Privacy Policy.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. Cookies typically are used to store user preferences or IDs. You do not have to use cookies, but if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use all portions of Calculator Alligator or all functionality of the Services (as defined below). 

#### Log Data

Log Data includes information sent to us by browsers including, for example, browser type, browser time, time of access, screen resolution, IP address, referring site URL, current site URL, and search strings; information sent to us by advertising exchanges in the form of bid requests, which may include the information above as well as information like auction identifiers, for the purpose of soliciting bids to place online ads.

#### Personal Information

Personal information (also sometimes called personal data) is information that is associated with an individual and enables that individual to be singled out.  Through the use of tags, sdks, and cookies, we collect personal information about you; that is, information that does not identify you directly (for example, NOT your name or email address) but that may indirectly identify your device. Under European privacy law, some information transmitted by cookies including Log Data are considered personal information. However, in most cases we may be unable to identify this data as belonging to you, especially if you have not registered for an account on the Site.

#### Site Services (“Services”)

This term refers broadly to the entire set of services that we provide through our web site, including the collection of information, the analysis of that information, the provision of that information and insights derived from that information, and the selection and placement of optimal advertisements and content based on that information.

### Information Collection and Use

#### Legal Basis for Collection and Use

In order to deliver our Services, we use the information described in this Privacy Policy as necessary for our legitimate interests. These legitimate interests include our interests in providing, improving, and customizing the Services and providing you with relevant advertising and content, unless those interests are overridden by your interests or fundamental rights and freedoms that require protection of personal information. We may share your information (as described in this Privacy Policy) where necessary to pursue our legitimate interests and those of our Partners in serving more useful and relevant advertising. You have the right to object to this processing where we rely on legitimate interests, which is described in the How To Object and Opt-Out section below.

In addition, where you have given us consent to use your information in certain ways, we will rely on your consent to process the information. You may revoke that consent at any time. Please see the How To Object and Opt Out section below for information as to how you may withdraw your consent.

#### Information Collected from the Site

When you visit our site, our servers record and collect Log Data automatically sent by your browser. We use the Log Data to monitor, analyze, administer, and improve the Site and our Services. As described below in the section Information Shared with Our Service Providers, we also allow some Partners to place cookies and tags on our Site.

If you contact us by email, we keep a record of your contact information and correspondence for as long as necessary to deal with your correspondence and the issues you raised. If you provide contact information to us, we may use that information to contact you with newsletters, marketing, or promotional materials. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications.

#### Information Collected through our Services

We do not link Log Data to your name, address, email, or phone number, or otherwise attempt to discover your identity. We employ appropriate organizational and technical security safeguards to keep information about you secure and to make it difficult for us to associate it with your identity.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

#### Information Shared with Our Partners

We share with third parties certain information, including Log Data, as part of providing and improving our products. For example, we disclose some of this data to companies involved in ad delivery or ad viewability. Likewise, we disclose some of this data in order to provide or facilitate site audience measurement, traffic analysis, or demographic analysis, and to enable websites to provide their advertisers with audience segments that are appropriate for their products or services.

If you sign up for an account on the Site, information such as your name and email address may be shared with third parties for the purposes of communicating with you (for example, for managing your account, informing you of changes to the site or other purposes).

#### Information Shared with Our Service Providers

We use third parties and affiliate companies to help us administer and improve our products. For example, these companies assist with hosting, data processing, database management, and administrative tasks on our behalf. These third parties and affiliates have access to information about you, including through the placement of cookies or tags on our Site, to perform these tasks on our behalf.

The site participates in the IAB Europe’s Transparency and Consent Framework to collect consent information within geographies that require it. The Site honors consumer choices that it receives via that framework and relays that consent to partners as per the framework’s guidelines.

#### Information Disclosed for Our Protection and the Protection of Others

It is our policy to protect you from having your privacy violated through abuse of the legal system. We reserve the right to disclose information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary: (i) to comply with any applicable laws, regulations, and valid subpoenas, warrants, and court orders; (ii) to protect the rights, property, and safety of ourselves, third parties, or the public in general; and (iii) to prevent or stop activity we consider to be illegal or unethical.

#### Information Disclosed in a Change of Ownership

Dadsworksheets.com, LLC may sell, transfer, or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including information we collect about you, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization, or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. We may also make certain information available to a potential investor or purchaser (and their advisers) in advance of any such transaction completion.

### Data Retention

We retain data for as long as necessary to provide our Services and for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. For example, we retain Log Data for up to 13 months. It is then permanently deleted. We may also retain information as is necessary to comply with our legal obligations, to resolve disputes, or to enforce our agreements.

### How to Object and Opt Out

If you prefer not to receive interest-based content and ads, you can object and opt-out by clicking at the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) and the Digital Advertising Alliance’s (DAA) Self-Regulatory Program. Each of these programs provides an opt-out feature where consumers can choose not to receive targeted advertising from any NAI or DAA affiliate. These links will take you to the [NAI opt out](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) and the [DAA opt out](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) pages. If you are located in the European Union, you may prefer to use the [EDAA opt out](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/).

### Accessing, Changing, or Deleting Your Information

If you are a registered user, you may review, update, correct, or delete the information in your registration profile by logging into your account. If you want to delete your account, please use the functions on the profile page.

If you are located in the EEA and we can properly identify you, you have a number of rights with regard to your personal information. For example, you have the right to access your information and to have inaccuracies in your personal information corrected. In many cases where we process your information, you may also have a right to restrict or limit the ways in which we use your information. You also have the right to object to the processing of your personal information and to have it deleted in certain circumstances. You also have a right to obtain a copy of your personal information in an easily accessible format. These functions are available on your profile page.

However, as outlined above, although we may collection some information in accordance with this Privacy Policy, if you do not sign up for an account, we don’t know who you are. Accordingly, if we receive a request from you and we cannot identify you (even if you provide us with additional information), we may not be able to assist you in exercising these rights.

### Data Security

We employ administrative, physical, and technical measures designed to protect the confidentiality and integrity of personal information that we hold. These measures may include encryption and employment of information storage security technologies to restrict access to our network. Please be aware that no method of transmitting information over the Internet or storing information is completely secure. We have procedures and security features in place to help keep your data secure once we receive it. Additionally, in some instances our Partners or others may provide information to us in unencrypted form.

### Our Policy Toward Children

The Site does not knowingly collect data from children under 13, and in the EEA under 16. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personal information without their consent, that parent or guardian should contact us. If we become aware that a child has provided us with personal information, we will delete such information from our files.

### Health and Sensitive Information

The Site does not knowingly collect or utilize any sensitive health-related information, such as, for example, information related to past or present medical conditions or prescriptions. In the EEA, the Site does not knowingly collect or utilize any Personal Information revealing racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, or trade union membership, genetic or biometric data for the purpose of uniquely identifying an individual, or data concerning an individual’s health, sex life, or sexual orientation.

### Data Control

The Site and Services are made available and provided to all persons by Dadsworksheets.com, LLC, an Arizona (United States) based limited liability corporation. Information or data provided to or gathered by the the Site or Services is controlled by Dadsworksheets.com, LLC.

### Changes to the Privacy Policy

Any information that we collect is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time that information is collected. We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time, so please check this page regularly for updates. If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we’ll notify you of those changes by posting them clearly on our website and/or by sending you an email or other notification, where feasible, and we’ll indicate when such changes will become effective.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please let us know.
